<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FoodieApp</string>
    <string name="title_placeholder" />
    <string name="news_placeholder" />
    <string name="meal_info_placeholder" />

    <string-array name="meal_titles">
        <item>Cheeseburger</item>
        <item>Pizza Pie</item>
        <item>Tempura Sushi</item>
        <item>Whole Chicken</item>
        <item>Waffles</item>
        <item>Grilled Salmon and Rice</item>
        <item>Lasagna</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="meal_info" >
        <item>Ahhh the Cheeseburger. Who doesnt like a nice burger on a afternoon huh? Maybe
        on the grill or in a barbeque. I personally like a burger with some nice onions, bacon, american cheese, lettuce, and some nice
        crunchy lettuce.</item>
        <item>The classic Pizza Pie. Pizza, dish of Italian origin consisting of a flattened disk of bread dough topped with some combination of
            olive oil, oregano, tomato, olives, mozzarella or other cheese, and many other ingredients, baked quickly—usually,
            in a commercial setting, using a wood-fired oven heated to a very high temperature—and served hot.</item>
        <item>Tempura Sushi. My favorite kind of sushi to be honest. The term tempura is a Japanese word used to refer to seafood
            or vegetables prepared by dipping them in a batter and deep frying them in hot oil.
            Tempura shrimp is a delectable dish in Japanese cuisine made by frying sweet and
            savoury shrimp with crispy batter and crumbs.</item>
        <item>Whole Chicken. Love putting this in my salad. Whole chicken which consists of breast,
            thigh, wings, neck and back. It may contain one liver, one stomach and one heart.
            It is ideal for oven or even for soup and stews, if cut in parts.</item>
        <item>Waffles, a breakfast delicacy. A waffle is a leavened batter or dough cooked between two hot plates
            of a waffle iron, patterned to give a characteristic size, shape,
            and grid-like surface impression. Waffles are cooked until they become
            golden-brown in color, with a crispy outer texture and a soft interior. </item>
        <item>Grilled Salmon and Rice, another delicacy. Salmon is easy, healthy, and
            delicious prepared in a simple marinade. Rice is the seed of a semi-aquatic grass (Oryza sativa) that is
            cultivated extensively in warm climates in many countries, including the United States,
            for its edible grain. It is a staple food throughout the world.</item>
        <item>Lasagna. One of my favorite meals ever. Lasagna (plural “lasagne”) is a flat and expanded pasta sheet,
            traditionally made in Italy with Parmigiano-Reggiano, Béchamel sauce, and ragù.
            Despite the traditional form still being popular, lasagna has taken on many different
            recipes over the years.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="meal_images" >
        <item>@drawable/cheeseburger</item>
        <item>@drawable/cheesepizza</item>
        <item>@drawable/shrimptempuraroll</item>
        <item>@drawable/roastedchickenlemon</item>
        <item>@drawable/waffles</item>
        <item>@drawable/grilledsalmon</item>
        <item>@drawable/lasagna</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="meal_calories">
        <item>303</item>
        <item>2000</item>
        <item>508</item>
        <item>2994</item>
        <item>436</item>
        <item>434</item>
        <item>336</item>
    </integer-array>


    <string-array name="meal_ingredients">
        <item>Ground Beef, American Cheese, 2 Burger Buns, Ketchup, Mayonnaise
        sliced red onion, sliced pickles, fresh lettuce</item>
        <item>1 ball of dough, fresh mozzarella, 2 tablespoons of basil leaves,
        Extra-virgin olive oil, 1 can of tomato sauce, grated parmesan
        </item>
        <item> Sushi Rice, 1 sheet Nori, Dry roasted seaweed, 3 pieces shrimp tempura prepared
            , 2 slices avocado, 3 teaspoons cream cheese (use the block cream cheese and cut into a couple long,
            rectangular slices, ½ cup flour, tempura batter, oil for frying</item>
        <item> Whole Chicken, Herbs and Whole Onion, garlic and butter, olive oil </item>
        <item> Eggs, flour, Milk, Oil, Sugar, Baking Powder, Salt, Vanilla, Cooking spray</item>
        <item> 1 1⁄2 - 2 lbs salmon fillets, 2 tablespoons teriyaki sauce, 1 tablespoon Worcestershire sauce,
            2 tablespoons lemon juice, 2 tablespoons brown sugar, 1 tablespoon Dijon mustard</item>

        <item>
        2 teaspoons extra virgin olive oil, 1 pound ground beef chuck, 1/2 medium onion,
            diced, 1/2 large bell pepper (green, red, or yellow), diced, 2 cloves garlic, minced
            1 can tomato sauce, 3 ounces tomato paste (half a 6-ounce can),
            1 can crushed tomatoes, 2 tablespoons chopped fresh oregano, or 2 teaspoons dried oregano,
            1/4 cup chopped fresh parsley, packed, 1 tablespoon Italian seasoning,
            1 pinch garlic powder and/or garlic salt, 1 tablespoon red or white wine vinegar
            1 tablespoon to 1/4 cup sugar, Salt
        </item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="meal_recipes">
        <item>https://www.recipetineats.com/cheeseburger-recipe/</item>
        <item>https://thefoodcharlatan.com/homemade-pizza-recipe/</item>
        <item>https://www.favfamilyrecipes.com/godzilla-rolls/#wprm-recipe-container-19810</item>
        <item>https://www.spendwithpennies.com/roast-chicken/</item>
        <item>https://www.allrecipes.com/recipe/22180/waffles-i/</item>
        <item>https://www.food.com/recipe/grilled-salmon-and-rice-332882</item>
        <item>https://www.simplyrecipes.com/recipes/lasagna/</item>
    </string-array>


    
    
</resources>